{"data":[{"question":"Mary and her husband wanted to give the old lady to a nice birthday present.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"her","b":"to give","c":"to","d":"nice","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"He is such famous that he has a great many fans.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"such","c":"has","d":"fans","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- So-> such","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The police caught he because he was involved in a robbery.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"police","b":"he","c":"because","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- He-> him","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"If he doesn't understand the lesson, his father often explains it for him.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"understand","b":"his","c":"often","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n\n- For-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Most of the building in this town are rather unattractive, but this church is an exception.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of","b":"building","c":"rather","d":"but","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Building-> buildings","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"She has a strongly determination to be a teacher.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"strongly","c":"determination","d":"be","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Strongly-> strong","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The government are trying playing down their involvement in the affair.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"playing","c":"their","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Playing-> to play","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The expansion of this factory will to create more employment to local people.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"expansion","b":"this","c":"to create","d":"local","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To create-> create","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"There is a chill striking me when I go alone in night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"striking","c":"when","d":"in","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- In-> at","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"English is the native or official language on one-fifths of the land area of the world.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"encountered","b":"haven't","c":"for","d":"times","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Times-> time","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}